SPY CLASSROOM
FILE: Lamplight Days
Heat Haze Palace...
It's unclear how true it is,
but it's said that the manor was once a hideout
belonging to the royal family
and was a palace in every sense of the word.
During the Pre-Impossible Mission Training
Nowadays, though...
Nothing works!
Not at all.
Your wire trap today was well-executed.
I could feel your training paying off.
Hooray?
Yes.
However,
the fact you aren't being as elegant and graceful as
a seafowl's plumage as it soars through a zephyr
is really kind of disappointing.
I didn't follow a word of that...
...but I could tell he was saying
we fell short of the mark.
We really are washouts, aren't we?
We've already been here for over ten days.
But every day, we keep losing!
We suck, yo!
At this rate, we're done for.
Don't be so hard on yourselves.
All of you are getting stronger.
I'm just so powerful it's hard to tell, that's all.
I'll be looking forward to your next attack.
Hey! At least untie the damn wires!
Undo them yourselves.
Consider it part of your training.
How unlucky...
Whoa, the wires didn't leave a single mark.
I guess that's a professional for you.
Color me surprised.
I never figured a meathead gorilla like you
would care about that kind of stuff.
Who you callin' a gorilla?
If I had to pick someone...
You would have expected me
to be the one who was concerned?
I mean, seduction is her area of expertise.
Honestly, I wasn't too worried.
There are plenty of men who get turned on
by rope burns and such in the bedroom.
You know, for someone who likes to play the cynic,
you're actually surprisingly childish.
Excuse me? I'll have you know I-
L-let's just drop it, okay?
I can't stand it when conversations get all raunchy!
Wait, for real?
More importantly, what should we
do for our next attack?
I've been giving it some thought,
and I say we all head into town together and-
Yeah, about that.
There's no reason to be so fixated
on working as a group.
She's right.
It might be a good idea for us each
to try our own thing for a bit.
I agree.
There isn't any rule that says
we always have to attack him as a team.
You cool with that, Leader?
The bath's all yours.
Roger that, yo!
The younger group will head on in, then.
C'mon, let's have a contest!
We'll see who can stay underwater the longest!
I wanted to take my bath alone...
I see, that's what you were talking about in the bath.
Yeah.
I know it's not a rule or anything,
but we don't have long before the Impossible Mission.
You would think that developing our teamwork
would be priority number one.
We were able to work together with
some success the other day,
but that doesn't change the fact that Lamplight is
an ad hoc team that only just came together.
And what's more, many of us have loud personalities.
Getting us all on the same page
will be easier said than done.
Getting in some solo training at this hour?
Your efforts are commendable, Sybilla.
I mean, I guess...
This is a problem.
As the team leader, what's a girl to do?
We need to talk, Leader.
Huh?
Wow, this is what your room looks like?
The furnishings are all so nice!
They're all right.
I was hoping to get the corner room,
but you went and snatched it up first.
Look, I won that lottery fair and square-
While I have you...
I must say, I'm shocked.
To think that you, of all people,
would be such a late bloomer.
Whether or not you have any actual experience,
your academy should have at least
taught you the basics of seduction.
I would have assumed it was right up your alley.
You have a cunning streak a mile long
and a heart devoid of shame.
Fl-flattery will get you nowhere, you know!
Ah, what a waste.
You even have the perfect assets for the job.
Oh, this will do just fine.
I'm going to give you a makeover, Lily.
What do you say to taking Teach down
with some seduction?
Men like him tend to go for the bashful, innocent type
over more confident women like me.
That flirtatious blush you're going for
right now is perfect.
I'm not going for anything!
I'm really not!
Think of how impressed we would be
if you got Teach to surrender.
"That's our leader for you!" we'd all say.
Y-you can talk it up all you like-
You'll do it for us, won't you...
Leader?
Come in.
S-so, um...
I need your help, Big Brother!
"Big Brother"?
I just remembered that I
was your little sister in a past life.
I-I was also a maid who loved serving you,
and every night, I would give you a massage
to ease your fatigue, just the two of us.
Now, come on, lie down!
Also, if you drink this before I start,
it will make the massage twice as effective, meow!
Lily, how much longer should
I keep playing along with this game?
If there's something troubling you,
I'd be happy to lend you an ear.
Please just forget this ever happened!
That sounds pretty rough.
That's why I told her I didn't want to do it!
What about Miss Thea?
What did she say?
Oh, get a load of this!
Well, I expected about as much.
I have to say, that man has the self-control of a monk.
It's all but unthinkable, from a man of his age.
Actually, how old is Teach?
Thank you for the valuable data, Leader.
She's the worst!
I didn't want to go along, but seduction is her specialty,
so I figured she knew what she was-
It's only the inside of the manor that's bugged,
so I think you're fine.
R-right...
That aside, it's nice how you young'uns
are working together so well.
I think Erna and Annette
really hit it off the other day.
I wouldn't be so sure...
I can't take it anymore.
It's Annette.
She keeps laying traps all over the place,
and I keep getting caught in them.
It just happened again.
Yeep!
Yeep, yeep, yeep!
Yeep.
How unlucky.
Ah, I hear that was a problem at her academy, too.
She got good grades,
but she kept messing around and
building bizarre spy tools.
Surely, she's just setting the traps
to make Teach say "I surrender," right?
No way.
She's doing it to torment me
so she can have a laugh.
She's dead to me!
Let's tail her.
It shouldn't be hard to get to the bottom of this.
I don't know why, but the carpet is bulging up.
It is? I don't see any-
I should step on it.
How unlucky.
I think I get it.
Me too.
She's just really susceptible to that sort of thing.
If anything, I feel like she walked into that one.
Not on purpose, but still.
Wait, it's you again?!
Yeep!
That's annoying, yo.
I want someone else to get caught for a change.
How are you the person who's complaining here?!
I hate you.
It's probably six of one, half dozen of the other.
I want an apology, now.
I don't think there's anything really to worry about.
Now you're just talking nonsense, yo.
The team's a mess.
What do I do?
At this rate, the Impossible Mission...
is gonna wipe us all out?!
I can't let that happen!
Not when we've only just met,
and not when I finally have a chance
to escape how things were
and bloom into someone I can be proud of.
Is that you, Grete?
It is.
I brought you some dinner, Boss.
I see, thank you.
You should head back to your room
and get some sleep.
No, no.
You must be tired from being out so late,
so I should at least serve you.
I'm fine.
You should really go-
Please let me in.
I would very much like to serve you your dinner.
You making it was already more than kind enough.
Goodnight.
Was he worried that I was going to attack him?
I honestly just wanted to serve him dinner.
Now that I think about it,
has Teach ever eaten a meal with us?
He hasn't.
He always cooks for one and eats alone in his room.
You know, I've got a plan that
might just be worth trying.
FILE: Lamplight Days
I got trounced.
I ran into Klaus at the firing range earlier,
and he gave me some one-on-one coaching.
Let's play Russian Roulette.
I'll make you say, "I surrender," for sure.
I'm game.
Before we start, though...
you should put that bullet you just
slipped out of the chamber back in.
Put it back in.
I actually challenged him as well.
Want to keep going?
Nah, I surrender.
He got me good.
With the way billiards works,
I was so sure I had it in the bag.
Does that have something to do
with your special ability?
The one you haven't told us about yet?
If we take Teach on separately,
he's just going to crush us!
That's why I, Wunderkind Lily, came up with a plan!
"Wunderkind"?
Just ignore that part.
Let her have it.
But Wunderkind or not,
I won't be able to carry it out alone.
I'm gonna need everyone's help.
What do you say?
Will you lend me a hand?
Not like we've got much of a choice, yeah?
Seconded.
We all in?
Let's do this!
Then it's settled.
Teach has a mission today,
so he'll be heading into town.
When he does...
This is Fool.
The target stopped by a restaurant.
This is Pandemonium.
The target left the restaurant.
Resuming pursuit.
That figures, but we planned for this!
This is Meadow.
I told Mr. Bernard to stay far enough back
that Teach doesn't notice him.
If we make him believe he gave us the slip,
even a pro's gonna let his guard down.
B Team, use Mr. Bernard as a landmark
and follow Teach.
Roger that.
This is Daughter Dearest.
According to one of the restaurant's employees,
the boss has some foods he can't stand.
And also...
Oh hey, that's odd.
That patron didn't finish his espresso.
He might have had a stomachache.
I saw him clutching at his belly.
This is Dreamspeaker.
The target is looking at some ingredients and frowning.
This is Glint.
The target boarded a train at the station.
His mission today is probably in another town.
All units, return to base.
Send out the word!
Aye aye!
Thanks to everyone's hard work,
we were able to score some valuable intel.
According to my hypothesis,
the reason Teach never eats with us...
Is 'cuz he's got food allergies, yeah?
Hey! Don't go stealing your leader's thunder!
It does make sense.
That's exactly the kind of information
a spy wouldn't want people to know.
That checks out, yo!
Then we'd better get started, Leader.
A-hem!
All right, everyone, let's get cooking!
Yeah!
Those are some fancy knife skills.
Get out of my face.
You're in the way.
Damn, I didn't know you were so handy in the kitchen.
Cooking is a basic spy skill.
For the tournée-cut carrots, do these look all right?
That's brilliant.
Looks like everything's going smoothly over there.
The problem is those two...
How's it coming?
Don't talk to me.
I have to be careful when I'm frying the shrimp.
Got it!
I've got a great tool to grind them up with, yo!
Yeep?! That's ridiculous.
Why do your inventions all have to be so destructive?
Hey, you've got some sauce on your cheek.
Here, let me get it.
K-keep your hands to yourself!
They'll be fine.
Even when she acts mad like that,
she's actually enjoying herself.
Yeah, I can tell.
All right, you two, listen up!
The others are almost done with the soup,
so I was thinking we could get started
making a milk pudding to have for dessert.
I'll help.
Me too, yo!
The two of them really are adorable.
For sure.
Hey, Lily, what gives?
You haven't been helpin' anyone.
I'm the supervisor...
or, like, the cheerleader?
Get working, dammit!
Go set the table!
Sybilla, the meat's burning.
It's burning!
You all made this for me?
Yeah! We figured you'd be
tuckered out from your mission.
Your subordinates cooked it for you
out of the goodness of their hearts
and packed it full of love.
Go on, dig in!
Based on what we learned from tailing him...
...Klaus's weaknesses...
...that is, the foods he avoids...
...are beef...
...shrimp, and anything with dairy!
Come on, eat it.
Eat it up, yo!
Either that, or surrender!
Magnificent.
That was just what I was craving.
It... It was to your liking, Boss?
It was.
Thank goodness!
Hold up, that ain't good at all!
What the hell's goin' on here?!
He pulled one over on us.
He knew everything we were up to.
All those things we learned while tailing him...
...were stuff he wanted us to find out.
That conversation those waiters had
was probably his doing, too.
What do we do now?
We got carried away and cooked way too much food.
Ooh! I'm starving, yo!
I'm hungry, too.
Taking into account what I learned today,
the best way to split up the team
would be into those three groups.
Meals are something you eat with your family.
The more you share the same table,
the deeper your bonds grow.
I really screwed the pooch on this one...
Don't be so hard on yourself.
She's right, Leader.
You mean it?
You're really accepting someone like me
as your leader?
Yeah, basically.
I mean, Klaus did appoint you.
That guy pisses me the hell off!
The way he's always so goddamn composed...
I mean, how old is he even?
I actually know this one.
I asked him when we were out shopping together.
And?
He's twenty.
Shit, for real?
That's basically the same age as us.
In that case, I have an idea.
Yeah, I just thought up a plan, too.
I've got a special new creation up my sleeve for this!
This time, we'll make Teach surrender for sure!
Together, as a team!
Let's do this!
Yeep!
I expect they'll be spending the evening in high spirits
strengthening their bonds with each other.
It will be cozy, like a family.
But my family, Inferno, is gone.
Now, I've lost my reason to share a table with people.
Hey, Leader, do you have a minute?
Yup! Coming!
Leader...
You called?
Leader!
On it, on it, on it!
A trusty leader's day starts early,
and the work never ends.
From the way you're acting,
I guess you managed to quash your worries.
Huh? I was worried about something?
What's with that look?
You got something you wanna say?
No...
Never change, Lily.
That indominable spirit of yours is your greatest virtue.
You know it!
I'm gonna indomitably herald a new era.
With Wunderkind Lily at its head,
Lamplight's going to lead the charge.
I would expect nothing less.
Make sure you all train hard today.
Our inaugural Impossible Mission
is just around the corner.
You got it!